http://scout.wisc.edu/privacy-policy

Scout Privacy Policy - Last Modified September 14, 2012
The Internet Scout Research Group (Scout) provides links to resources for faculty, staff, librarians, students, and others for use in educational settings or in their pursuit of lifelong learning.
The privacy policy set forth here refers solely to the Internet Scout Web site. The policy describes how we gather and use information you provide to us while you are using the Internet Scout site. This policy does not pertain to information you provide to us off-line. Please read over this policy carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to contact us at scout@scout.wisc.edu.
We may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the law, our practices, and the features of Internet Scout. As a result, you should review the Privacy Policy from time to time, so that you are up to date on our most current version.
Gathering and Use of Information
Internet Scout will never distribute subscriber emails to anyone else unless required by law.
To register with Internet Scout and gain access to the tools available through the site, you must supply us with some personally identifiable information. this information is only used to help us personalize the site for your experience.
Internet Scout may use elements of the information you provide us (such as area of study or primary teaching discipline, but not any personally identifiable information such as your name, school name, or email address) for internal and promotional purposes.
Aggregated Data
Internet Scout keeps traffic records to determine information such as which pages are most popular, which browsers are most used, how long users spend on the Web site, and which sites they have come from. This helps us understand our audience, but is not matched in any way to personal data that we may also receive.
External Links
You will find links from Internet Scout to selected Web sites with content of interest to our users. These external links are operated by third parties who independently produce, maintain, and monitor these sites. Internet Scout does not control and is not responsible for the content of these sites.
You should review the privacy policies of third party sites for information regarding their collection and use of personally identifiable information as their policies may differ from ours.
Acceptance of Internet Scout Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Internet Scout Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of Internet Scout following posted changes to these terms means that you have accepted those changes.
